第十三字幕：
坚持住
The No.13 subtitile:
Oh,hold on.
第十三字幕：
我来了
The No.13 subtitile:
I'm coming.
第十三字幕：
在工作环境中好好利用
The No.13 subtitile:
Increased productivity
第十三字幕：
人体功学  可以提高生产效率哦
The No.13 subtitile:
Through ergonomically beneficial surroundings.
第十三字幕：
说到功能分化的精神
The No.13 subtitile:
Well,in the spirit of ergonomy--
第十三字幕：
有那个词儿吗
The No.13 subtitile:
Is that even a word?
第十三字幕：
功能分化是设备设计领域
The No.13 subtitile:
Ergonomy is the applied science
第十三字幕：
的十三项应用技术  迈克
The No.13 subtitile:
Of equipment design,michael.
第十三字幕：
好吧
The No.13 subtitile:
Okay.
第十三字幕：
那么说到  变形的精神
The No.13 subtitile:
Well,then in the spirit of...origami,
第十三字幕：
你想过把你的后座
The No.13 subtitile:
You ever thinking about making your backseat
第十三字幕：
变形成十三张床吗  凯特
The No.13 subtitile:
Into a bed,kitt?
第十三字幕：
我恐怕你会邀请陌生人过来哦
The No.13 subtitile:
I'm afraid you'd be tempted to invite strangers.
第十三字幕：
你是说"浪荡小妞"吧  凯特
The No.13 subtitile:
You mean "hoochies," kitt.
第十三字幕：
行为不端的妇女  你说的没错
The No.13 subtitile:
Undesirable females,yes.
第十三字幕：
这个小宝贝  在扶手上
The No.13 subtitile:
This puppy has got a cooler
第十三字幕：
装有冷柜哦
The No.13 subtitile:
Built into the armrest
第十三字幕：
还有大屏幕的遥控器呢
The No.13 subtitile:
And a remote for the big screen.
第十三字幕：
这可太棒了
The No.13 subtitile:
That is sweet.
第十三字幕：
椅子应该放在那边
The No.13 subtitile:
Chair belongs on the other side.
第十三字幕：
我喜欢它放这儿
The No.13 subtitile:
I like it where it is.
第十三字幕：
把它挪开  快点儿
The No.13 subtitile:
Move it,stretch.
第十三字幕：
中国的风水学里说明
The No.13 subtitile:
The chinese system of feng shui
第十三字幕：
祖伊选的位置
The No.13 subtitile:
Would indicate that zoe's placement
第十三字幕：
能带来更好的气
The No.13 subtitile:
Provides for better chi.
第十三字幕：
你可真有禅意  凯特
The No.13 subtitile:
Very zen of you,kitt.
第十三字幕：
我们在这儿可以多用用东方哲学嘛
The No.13 subtitile:
We could use a little more eastern philosophy around here.
第十三字幕：
听明白么  更好的气
The No.13 subtitile:
See? better chi.
第十三字幕：
快点啊
The No.13 subtitile:
Chop chop.
第十三字幕：
你顶谁的班当上领导了
The No.13 subtitile:
Who died and made you boss?
第十三字幕：
那肯定是阿莱克斯·托雷斯
The No.13 subtitile:
That would be alex torres.
第十三字幕：
我发现你已经在享受休闲时光了啊
The No.13 subtitile:
hmm,I see you're already enjoying your downtime.
第十三字幕：
我还没开始享受呢
The No.13 subtitile:
Oh,I have not yet begun to enjoy.
第十三字幕：
有什么地方想去吗
The No.13 subtitile:
Going anywhere special?
第十三字幕：
有啊
The No.13 subtitile:
Oh,yeah.
第十三字幕：
有个小小的感性之旅
The No.13 subtitile:
A little sentimental journey.
第十三字幕：
等等  我们要去什么地方吗
The No.13 subtitile:
Wait,we get to go somewhere?
第十三字幕：
-折扣商场  -做SPA去
The No.13 subtitile:
Outlet mall.  spa day.
第十三字幕：
你们在开玩笑  是吧
The No.13 subtitile:
You guys are kidding,right?
第十三字幕：
我要隐忍  沉淀十三下自己
The No.13 subtitile:
I'm going to get mellow and be zen.
第十三字幕：
你是说"我们"  迈克
The No.13 subtitile:
You mean "we," michael.
第十三字幕：
是我们  我们十三起去  凯特
The No.13 subtitile:
Yes,we. we are going,kitt.
第十三字幕：
回去那个特别的
The No.13 subtitile:
Back to a special place.
第十三字幕：
充满魔力的地方
The No.13 subtitile:
A magical place.
第十三字幕：
我们自己的小欢乐窝
The No.13 subtitile:
Our own little happy place.
第十三字幕：
迈克要带我去十三个酒吧
The No.13 subtitile:
Michael is taking me to a bar.
第十三字幕：
谁会想去那儿啊
The No.13 subtitile:
Who'd have thunk it?
第十三字幕：
我想去酒吧
The No.13 subtitile:
I want to go to a bar.
第十三字幕：
可不是十三般的酒吧哦  是桑尼's
The No.13 subtitile:
oh,no,not just any bar. sonny's.
第十三字幕：
我知道了
The No.13 subtitile:
Oh,I get it.
第十三字幕：
你爸带我过去  喝了我的第十三杯啤酒
The No.13 subtitile:
Your dad took me there for my first beer.
第十三字幕：
我爷爷也带我爸去喝过
The No.13 subtitile:
And his dad took him there for his.
第十三字幕：
是附近的十三个地方
The No.13 subtitile:
It's a neighborhood institution.
第十三字幕：
十三杯冷佳酿  啤酒豆  现场音乐
The No.13 subtitile:
A cold brew,beer nuts,live music.
第十三字幕：
是桑尼·尼尔桑开的
The No.13 subtitile:
Run by sonny nelson.
第十三字幕：
是个好酒保  更是个好人
The No.13 subtitile:
Amazing bartender,even better guy.
第十三字幕：
我好几年没去了
The No.13 subtitile:
I haven't been there in years,
第十三字幕：
可我跟你说把  要想减压
The No.13 subtitile:
But I can tell you that there is no better place
第十三字幕：
没别的地方比那儿更好了
The No.13 subtitile:
To de-stress.
第十三字幕：
听着棒极了
The No.13 subtitile:
Sounds awesome.
第十三字幕：
我确实肩负着极大的压力
The No.13 subtitile:
I'm a veritable cornucopia of stress.
第十三字幕：
我还记得
The No.13 subtitile:
From what I remember,
第十三字幕：
桑尼有个女儿
The No.13 subtitile:
Sonny had a daughter.
第十三字幕：
是啊  茱莉 尼尔桑.
The No.13 subtitile:
Yeah,julie nelson.
第十三字幕：
我想她上了医学院
The No.13 subtitile:
She went to med school I think
第十三字幕：
在东部的什么地方
The No.13 subtitile:
Somewhere back east.
第十三字幕：
-没错  -玩的开心
The No.13 subtitile:
Right. have a great time.
第十三字幕：
你们也是  伙计们
The No.13 subtitile:
You too,guys.
第十三字幕：
喂
The No.13 subtitile:
Hello!
第十三字幕：
怎么啦
The No.13 subtitile:
Hi.
第十三字幕：
我们最好告诉他
The No.13 subtitile:
We better tell him.
第十三字幕：
不然他要崩溃了
The No.13 subtitile:
Or else he might have a breakdown.
第十三字幕：
拜托有人出来说句话啊
The No.13 subtitile:
Somebody please say something.
第十三字幕：
听着  我们正在轮班
The No.13 subtitile:
Look,we're going on rotation.
第十三字幕：
每个人都能轮到机会减压
The No.13 subtitile:
Everyone's gonna get a chance to decompress.
第十三字幕：
首先  迈克能休息几天
The No.13 subtitile:
First,mike's gonna take a couple days.
第十三字幕：
然后是你  然后是祖伊  然后是我
The No.13 subtitile:
And then you,and then zoe,and then me.
第十三字幕：
什么时候开始
The No.13 subtitile:
When's this all gonna start?
第十三字幕：
问你领导去吧
The No.13 subtitile:
Ask your boss.
第十三字幕：
好吧  十三点也不好笑
The No.13 subtitile:
Okay,not funny.
第十三字幕：
不  比利  很好笑啊
The No.13 subtitile:
No,billy,it was funny.
第十三字幕：
比我印象中乱点儿
The No.13 subtitile:
A little rougher than I remembered.
第十三字幕：
我必须承认  我多少有点
The No.13 subtitile:
I must admit,I'm somewhat concerned
第十三字幕：
担心你  迈克
The No.13 subtitile:
For you,michael.
第十三字幕：
我不会有事的  凯特  呆在这儿
The No.13 subtitile:
I'll be okay,kitt. just stay close.
第十三字幕：
要忍哦
The No.13 subtitile:
And be zen.
第十三字幕：
我会试试看
The No.13 subtitile:
I will try.